<versions>
	<version id="1.3.0">
		<features>
			<feature>Added support for custom log targets. These can be activated by Olog.activateTargets(). IMPORTANT: See notes!</feature>
			<feature>Simplified utility panel</feature>
			<feature>Added check for updates to utility panel</feature>
			<feature>Added clear to utility panel to clear all text from log window</feature>
			<feature>Added data type comparison to assert()</feature>
			<feature>Added support for getters and setters in Olog.describe()</feature>
			<feature>Added warning for key binding overrides</feature>
		</features>
		<fixes>
			<fix>Fixed return boolean on assert</fix>
			<fix>Fixed breakPoint args. Primitive values are appended to the single line log message, one object is displayed with full description and one object followed by all string args will display a description filtered against the property names passed after the first argument.</fix>
		</fixes>
		<notes>Log targets replaces the event dispatching functionality of Olog. OlogEvent is removed and you can no longer call addEventListener on Olog. Instead create a custom log target that implements ILogTarget and pass it to Olog.activateTargets()</notes>
	</version>
	<version id="1.2.9">
		<features>
			<feature>Added enableAssertions as a property on Olog to enable/disable asserts in code</feature>
			<feature>Added argument maxDurationMS to newTimeMarker for optional tracking of how operations over- or undershoot their allowed execution times</feature>
		</features>
		<fixes>
			<fix>Olog now only captures key presses for filtering lines when it has stage focus</fix>
			<fix>RegEx bugfix in traceCallStack</fix>
		</fixes>
	</version>
	<version id="1.2.8">
		<features>
			<feature>Added simple assert() function</feature>
			<feature>getCallee will now insert "constructor" instead of repeating the class name</feature>
		</features>
		<fixes>
			<fix>Corrected a small spelling mistake in noMethodBodyWarning()</fix>
			<fix>Fixed introspection in breakPoint()</fix>
			<fix>Corrected property name limit lits in Olog.describe</fix>
		</fixes>
	</version>
	<version id="1.2.7">
		<features>
			<feature>Olog can now be enabled to dispatch the event OlogEvent.OLOG_OUT with each message written to the log. This event contains the full parsed Oline vo for external use.</feature>
			<feature>Olog can now be enabled send log messages to the JS console with console.log, console.warn and console.error depending on the severity og the message.</feature>
		</features>
	</version>
	<version id="1.2.6">
		<features>
			<feature>traceDisplayList now displays child index for each child</feature>
			<feature>traceDisplayList now supports display object containers that are not on stage, in which case child index is displayed as "X".</feature>
			<feature>traceDisplayList now runs backwards to display children in the correct stacking order in the log window</feature>
		</features>
	</version>
	<version id="1.2.5">
		<features>
			<feature>traceDisplayList now supports argument-less functions as the property argument</feature>
			<feature>Option expandArrayItems (toggle, default: false) to enable parsing of array items individually instead of toString value</feature>
			<feature>Option colorizeColorStrings (toggle, default: true) to make Olog display detected color strings (e.g. 0xff0000) in the color they describe</feature>
		</features>
	</version>
	<version id="1.2.4">
		<fixes>
			<fix>Fixed a regex match bug with traceDisplayList</fix>
		</fixes>
	</version>
	<version id="1.2.3">
		<fixes>
			<fix>Fixed an issue causing context menu to disappear when Olog.window was added directly to stage</fix>
		</fixes>
	</version>
	<version id="1.2.2">
		<features>
			<feature>Added backwards compatible support for global error handling</feature>
		</features>
		<fixes>
			<fix>Corrected formatting issue with traceDisplayList</fix>
		</fixes>
	</version>
	<version id="1.2.1">
		<features>
			<feature>Added key binding utility. Allows for calling functions by typing a predefined character sequence.</feature>
			<feature>Added Olog.traceDisplayList to output a tree structure representation of the display list from a given container</feature>
		</features>
	</version>
	<version id="1.2.0">
		<features>
			<feature>Added shorthand function otrace()</feature>
			<feature>Added utility function breakPoint() for logging virtual break points</feature>
			<feature>Added utility function nullFunction for use in yet to be assigned callback situations</feature>
			<feature>Added utility fucntion getCallee() for returning the string of a point in the call stack</feature>
			<feature>Added utility function noMethodBodyWarning() for indicating an empty method and its position</feature>
			<feature>Log messages from Olog itself now have a proper origin</feature>
			<feature>More thorough introspection when using describe method. More properties found.</feature>
			<feature>Added automatic regular trace output via property enableRegularTraceOutput</feature>
			<feature>Added memory usage display in title bar</feature>
			<feature>Update check is off by default</feature>
			<feature>Describe robustness</feature>
			<feature>More info when tracing runtime info</feature>
			<feature>Added line wrapping preference</feature>
		</features>
		<fixes>
			<fix>Resolved issue where prefs pane would stay open after minimizing</fix>
			<fix>Resolved issue with filtering on log level</fix>
			<fix>General stability fixes</fix>
			<fix>More compressed log statements with IOErrorEvents</fix>
			<fix>Resolved text coloring and object name bug with describe</fix>
		</fixes>
	</version>
	<version id="1.1.0">
		<features>
			<feature>Added truncation options for maxChars and multiline</feature>
		</features>
		<notes>Trucation is turned off by default. Use Olog.setTruncation(multilines true/false, maxChars)</notes>
	</version>
	<version id="1.0.0">
		<features>
			<feature>Brighter coloring for easier reading</feature>
			<feature>More sensible handling of ErrorEvents</feature>
		</features>
		<fixes>
			<fix>Window no longer empty after password prompt</fix>
			<fix>cr() method now defaults to 1 empty line</fix>
			<fix>Silent failing of update check</fix>
		</fixes>
	</version>
	<version id="0.9b"></version>
</versions>